<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Group 6 Project: Production Sites&#39; Ecological Footprint</title>
    <link>https://ptds2021-g6.netlify.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Group 6 Project: Production Sites&#39; Ecological Footprint</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ptds2021-g6.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://ptds2021-g6.netlify.app/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ptds2021-g6.netlify.app/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Goals and Impact All of us are aware of the urgent need to reduce our individual ecological footprint by reducing our overall consumption, shift our purchasing habits, recycle more, invest in renewable energies and globally contribute to a common goal: a cleaner planet. Even though world leaders gather to unify and work as a united front towards sustainable changes with the ultimate goal to slow climate change, we still currently detect many problems surrounding the topic of sustainability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ptds2021-g6.netlify.app/data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ptds2021-g6.netlify.app/data/</guid>
      <description>Key terms   Ecological Footprint: &amp;ldquo;A measure of how much area of biologically productive land and water an individual, population, or activity requires to produce all the resources it consumes and to absorb the waste it generates, using prevailing technology and resource management practices. The Ecological Footprint is usually measured in global hectares (gha). Because trade is global, an individual or country&amp;rsquo;s Footprint includes land or sea from all over the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ptds2021-g6.netlify.app/shiny/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ptds2021-g6.netlify.app/shiny/</guid>
      <description>Motivation Package G6 results from our interest in visualizing the impact of production (respectively consumption) on climate&amp;rsquo;s deterioration in the past 50 years throughout the world. The climate crisis is the direct consequence of the environmental resources&#39; over-consumption. Since the industrial revolution, innovations pushed industries to always consume more without anticipating facing limited resources and without considering their impact on the environment. Much later with the rise of impressive technological advancements, we have come to the realization that we have taken clean land, air, and water for granted and have damaged the abilities of land, air, and water to absorb society&amp;rsquo;s waste products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ptds2021-g6.netlify.app/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ptds2021-g6.netlify.app/team/</guid>
      <description>Group Members Our Programming Tools in Data Science team gathers three graduate students from the Master of Management at UNIL, one exchange student from Germany, WHU-Otto Beisheim School of Management and one exchange student from Louvain School of Management.
Each tab of this section highlights each member&amp;rsquo;s profile, chosen image, hobbies, and favorite quote.
Daniel Welz I am currently an Erasmus exchange student from Germany. In Germany, I was born in Stuttgart, however I am studying near Koblenz in the beautiful Rhine valley.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
